Geetha Sidhambaram

■ Indian, eligible to work in the UK

Profile

Have 4 years of experience in auditing projects, managing internal audits, supporting teams during external audits, monitoring non-compliance statuses, and maintaining organized documentation using an efficient internal tracking tool. Additionally, actively contributed as part of the agile process across various project teams.

I am seeking an opportunity to reinvigorate my career path after my break, and I am eager to prove my skills and contribute effectively.

Education

Bachelor of Science, Bharathiar University

Master of Science in Computer Science, Bharathiar University

Diploma in fine arts, Rockstartists Studio 🛮

UXUI Design, Buff Creative College Chennai 🛭

Full stack development,

GUVI GEEK NETWORK PRIVATE LIMITED 17

2007 - 2010 | Tamilnadu, India

2010 – 2012 | Tamilnadu, India

2022 - 2022 | Delhi, India

06/2019 - 10/2021 | Chennai, India

12/2023 - 12/2024 | Chennai, India

Skills

Figma Balsamiq

Invision SDLC

Agile Methodologies
User Research

Prototyping Wireframing

Wireframe

Responsive Design Information architecture

Front end UI Design

• HTML, CSS, javascript, React is CSS Frameworks

Mongodb, PostgresSQLAPI, PostmanBootstrap

• Github ChakraUI

Work Experience

Competitor analysis

UI/UX Designer, Freelancer (Beginner) https://www.behance.net/geethas ☑

04/2021 - present | London, India

ALTR - Community-based goal settings mobile app. ALTR is designed to help anyone to achieve their goals for self-improvement.

VilFresh - Redesigned e-commerce app that aims to bring village fresh products to urban citizens. The Vilfresh app allows you to buy a village fresh products like milk, fruits, and grocery items that come directly from the farmers. **M2M Builders** - Website design for building construction company.

Home Maker, Family

2016 – 2020 | Bangalore, India

- Learned programming skills like HTML and CSS.
- Completed diploma in Fine Arts course.
- Leading children in activities by reading stories, doing crafts, and helping to build social skills.

• Planned, assisted families, prepared nutritious meals.

Senior Quality Analyst, Infosys Ltd.

05/2013 - 03/2017 | Bangalore, India

- Audited projects based on the SDLC process and raising NC's if there are any deviations.
- Assisted with corrective action plans and monitored status project status, tracked NC's to Closure with RCA & CAPA.
- Audited code releases and artifacts.
- Guided various projects during external audits AT 801(SSAE).
- Conducted the change management audit and implemented it in a controlled manner.